http://www.fusiondox.com/idm2009/company/privacy-policy/

Home
»
Company
» Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The FusionDox Privacy Policy describes the type of information that FusionDox collects, and how we use, share and protect that information. Please be assured that FusionDox is committed to protecting your personal privacy. By using our web site and, where applicable, providing us with personal information, you confirm that you have read this policy and agree to its terms.
WHAT OUR PRIVACY POLICY COVERS
This Privacy Policy covers FusionDox 's treatment of personal information such as, but not limited to, your name, address, telephone number and email address, that FusionDox collects when you are on our web sites and when you use FusionDox services. This policy also covers our treatment of any personal information that FusionDox 's business partners share with FusionDox or that FusionDox may collect on a partner's site.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies, such as software publishers, that FusionDox does not own or control, or to people that FusionDoxdoes not employ or manage.
This site may contain links or references to other web sites outside of our control. Please be aware that IEXP has no control over these sites and our Privacy Policy does not apply to these sites.
COLLECTING INFORMATION
FusionDox may collect personal information when you purchase, activate or register a product, when you use certain other FusionDox products or services, request information, or when you visit our web sites. FusionDox may also receive personal information from our business partners.
FusionDox also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address and FusionDox cookie information.
FusionDox provides registration, activation, and e-commerce services to software publishers and other customers. In connection with providing those services, FusionDox shares personal information that has been collected in the course of providing those services with those software publishers and other customers.
When you register or activate a product from one of our publishers, we may ask for your name, company, postal address and email address. FusionDox may also ask for other personal information at the request of the individual publisher. We store all this information on behalf of the publisher.
USING AND SHARING INFORMATION
FusionDox may send personal information about you to other companies or people when permitted or required by law, including when:
We have your consent to share such information;
We need to share the information with companies who have similar privacy policies and who sub-contract to FusionDox to provide a product or service to you;
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process.
COOKIES
A "cookie" is a small piece of information that is placed on your computer's hard drive to customize your web experience. We may use FusionDox cookies to record what pages you have accessed and how many times you visit us. These cookies cannot be used to obtain personal information about you or to access information on your computer. Most internet browsers include preference settings that notify you when, and control whether, cookies are transferred to your computer. You can choose to disable the cookie function on your browser to deny acceptance of cookies. However, some of the features on our site may require that the cookie function in your browser be enabled in order for the feature to be fully functional.
IP ADDRESS
Your IP (internet Protocol) address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the internet. This address does not contain any personal information about you. Your IP address is used to help tracking during a particular session and to gather broad demographic data.  At FusionDox we also use it to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our site.
KEEPING THE INFORMATION SECURE
FusionDox uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions throughout our service offering and all communications with software publishers and third-party service providers.
We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your personal information.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
FusionDox may, at our discretion, amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our web site.
WHO TO CONTACT
If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, you may contact us at the location below:
Schwabe Enterprises LLC
220 E Jackson St
New Holland PA 17557
United States of America
or email us at:
info@fusiondox.com
Company Menu
Company
Partners
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
How to Purchase
Contact
FusionDox
http://www.fusiondox.com
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
Contact
©2010-2013 Schwabe Enterprises LLC, All Rights Reserved
FusionDox, fusiondox.com, and related brands using "fusiondox" are service marks of Schwabe Enterprises LLC and may not be used without express written permission.
